partysupplieshut.com 2010-12-19

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for PartySuppliesHut.com

The privacy of our visitors to PartySuppliesHut.com is important to us. 

At PartySuppliesHut.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit PartySuppliesHut.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on PartySuppliesHut.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. Give you’re soon to be husband the best gift ever. Surprised him with a scrap books with your initials and wedding date on the very top of the scrap book, leave extra room at the very end for upcoming wedding pictures. This will amaze him as you put much of your time to get it together and to look perfect.

Do enjoy the season with free party games:
